[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1, "question": "Piers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 2, "answer": "Anderson, thank you very much and we are leading on the breaking news tonight.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Amanda Knox"]}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "RP", "CC", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 23, "question": "What are the next few days going to hold for them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "Well, I think, Piers, they're going to try to literally hide to try to find some home where the media won't be staking out and trying to follow every move Amanda Knox makes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amanda", "Meredith", "Amanda"], "LOCATION": ["Meredith"]}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "And, what are y our views as a family friend of Amanda?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "Well, I think that -- well, I know that Amanda liked Meredith and that they were -- they were good friends and that's why they became roommates, that's why they decided to live together and Amanda felt great emotion around what happened to Meredith.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "VBN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "Are you, from a purely legal point of view, satisfied that justice has been done now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "One hundred percent I believe that justice has been done and I'm glad that she never gave up hope because if hope dies then that's the end for someone in prison.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "Is it simply a question of Meredith Kercher is British, Amanda Knox is American and it's a kind of geographic thing here where the British feel a greater affinity, perhaps, to the Kercher family and their case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "No, I don't, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Meredith Kercher", "Amanda Knox", "Kercher"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "Do you think she emerges with a clean character or with a stain on her character?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "I think she emerges with many questions, frankly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "Again, on the legal point, when she was found guilty and convicted and sentenced to a three year sentence, not a small period of time by any means, for this defamation, how seriously should we be taking that from a legal point of view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "CC", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "Well, she's served -- it's time served and I think that was the least of her problems.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "But does she know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Well, we may never know, I'm afraid.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "How could you possibly get any happier?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": ".", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Fridays"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "Why have you selected Friday as a day of great joy and happiness?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Well, Piers, for the most people, the studies show that people are happier on Fridays.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Monday"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "JJR", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "I think people are looking for the weekends, looking forward to it, getting to relax, you know, done with work and, you know, I've also read, Piers, where there's more heart attacks on Monday than any other day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "What about the poor guy who's trapped in a factory job or something or maybe has no job who, just through lack of opportunity and bad circumstance, is unhappy because he can't get out of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WP", ",", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Well, Piers, to me, faith is all about learning to be happy where you are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Do you believe, fundamentally, that money can make people happier?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "You know...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Victoria, you're shaking your head, why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Well, I mean, it helps, I mean, it helps but, no, I don't -- I've seen people who are very wealthy and they're unhappy, they don't have good relationships, they may even have bad health and ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "Why can poverty stricken people sometimes find joy in their lives?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "I think there's not so many distractions.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Or is he always this content happy chap?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Angry, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "CC", "WP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "What gets his goat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Well, I don't really think he flips out but what -- he likes things to be right, you know, and, you know, I've watched him when things aren't right and he chooses to see the best in the situation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "When's the last time you heard him -- when's the last time you heard him shout, Victoria, come on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Never.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Victoria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 178, "question": "You've never heard him shout?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "No, he's never shouted ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "IN", "PRP", ":", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "He's never shouted?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "...and if you -- listen, if you live with me and you don't shout, you're pretty good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "Do you never shout at anybody?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "No, no, that's not my personality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 198, "question": "Let me just clarify, you've never shouted in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "Well, I probably have, you know...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "When was the last time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "...I can't remember.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 205, "question": "What's the look?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "It's like ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday"]}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "So, what -- what frustrates in the noisy, what can ruin your Friday?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WP", ":", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "You know, I don't know if it would ruin my Friday but I -- like she said, I like things to be right, I like, you know, I like organization.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Have you ever had a fist fight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "I never have -- I never have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "Not even when you were a kid?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "Well, probably with my brother, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "Never actually -- have you ever been punched in the face?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "Have you ever been punched in the face?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "You have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "How do you explain that a just God can allow these kind of atrocities to happen, ruining so many lives?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "DT", "RB", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "You know, it's difficult, Piers, but the world we live in is not a perfect world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 253, "question": "Has it ever -- did your faith ever get dented?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ":", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "You know, it really...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "What do you say to people, again, who might come to you and say, I -- I can't continue having this faith because some appalling thing has happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "You know what, that happens from time to time but, again, I go back to the fact that, you know what, having faith means you're going to have unanswered questions.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "What do you say to them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "What I say is this, God's got you in the palm of his hand.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "Victoria, have you ever had your faith dented?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Well, no, I've never -- I never have, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "WP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "How do you have -- how do you have moments, for example, when something bad has happened, you know, in your life or something that's really affected you badly and you've prayed to God to have that situation end in a happy way and then it hasn't, your prayers haven't been answered, in that circumstance do you not feel slightly let down?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "NN", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "POS", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Well, you know what, I can't tell God what to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Do you ever watch yourself back on TV?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "ORGAN: Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "I do still edit them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "NN", "RB", "CC", "RB", "MD", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "How have you developed that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Well, my mother has had a great memory and when I started, you know, my dad just spoke extemporaneously and just would go and I couldn't do that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "What do you think of the whole issue?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "You know, it's a complicated issue, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "A life for a life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Well, I don't -- I don't know that that's -- you know, I -- it's -- it's hard for me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "You can't be the man who influences millions of people and sit on the fence about key moral issues like that, key moral stroke ethical issues and you've got to have a view haven't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Well, I think the thing is, is we have a justice system and I believe in our system of justice, number one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "RB", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 346, "question": "If I asked you about abortion, what would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "...well, abortion, I -- I feel stronger about because it -- I feel like...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "CC", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "What's your view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "...my view is that every baby should live, that, you know, that God's created that life and, so, again, that's what I feel strongly about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "CC", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Should there not be a more consistent view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Well, I think there could be when you say may or may not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "WDT", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Is homosexuality a sin, in your eyes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "Yes, I've always believed, Piers, the scriptures shows that it's a sin, but, you know, I'm not one of those that are out there to bash homosexuals and tell them that they're terrible people and all that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "VBD", ":", "JJ", "POS", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "What's your view now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "You know, Piers, it really never changes because mine was -- mine's based out of the scripture.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "I mean, like everything else, doesn't it have to move with the times and isn't it down again to people like you to interpret it in a way that evolves when you're known as a very progressive preacher?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "What if Texas eventually, in a moment it's an unlikely place I would imagine to bring this in, but it may change with enough pressure, Texas brings in a law that same-sex marriage is permissible, how would you feel then if it's the law of the land?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNP", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "-NONE-", "VBP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Well, you know what, I'm going to respect the law and I'm going to respect gay people like I do now, you know, have plenty of people that come to our church and friends, I would call, that are gay so I'm going to respect that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Texas", "Texas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "CC", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "You could never do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "No, it would be against what I believe the scripture teaches and, so, that's where I think the rub comes in with people like myself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 400, "question": "I mean, could you ever imagine attending a gay marriage between two people who come to your church, for example, if they invited you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "Well, I think if it was that easy, that we would have figured it out by now but it's been overthrown, states go for it and then they overthrow it, so it's very difficult for ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NN", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "Would I accept one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "Two gay people who attend your church invite you to their wedding.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "You would?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "Well, I don't -- you know, if I had time I would.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Joel, would you go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "If they were friends of mine...", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Could you be seen to do -- could you be photographed at such an event?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Well, I would not...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "...but, I'm -- I'm conservative, you know, that's who I've always been.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "You would say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "I like to vote on the candidate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "...who would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "...good thing I don't have to right now because it's too early in the race.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 468, "question": "What do you think people most care about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "JJS", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "I think -- are you talking about political issues ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ":", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "When people come to your church, what are -- what's really concerning them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "They care about their relationships -- their relationships, their finances, and their health.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Do you think politicians, today, are doing the right kind of thing or are they too busy scuffling with each other in Washington to understand clearly, as you've just defined it, what the real issues are for people in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "Yes, I think they're squabbling too much.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"], "LOCATION": ["Washington", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "JJS", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "PRP", ":", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "When you see them all ranting and raving and being deliberately obstructive to getting things done, what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VBG", "NNS", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "Well, I think, like most Americans, I would hope that they would work together and, you know, what I -- what I see that's difficult these days is any kind of compromise and, you know, it's hard to get 100 percent of what you want.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ":", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "Would you be comfortable with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "You know what, I'm comfortable with -- that would not stop me from voting for somebody.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Are there aspects to Mormonism which you find offensive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "NNP", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "I don't know a lot about it and here I go again but I don't know a lot...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", ":", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "How can you keep saying that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "...I don't know a lot about it but here -- here's the thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Like what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "I don't know -- I don't...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Jesus", "Jesus"]}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", ":", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", ":", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", ":", "TO", "PRP", ",", "DT", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Well, what are the things about Mormonism which are awkward for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "You know what, I don't know enough about their -- their beliefs to -- to point out what they are, to articulate it well but here's what I -- here's what I believe that, you know, Mitt Romney says he believes that Jesus is the Son of God, that he believes Jesus is his savior, that's the -- to me, those are the foundational things, when I look at somebody, could I vote for them, do they believe, you know, in the major things like me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Could you vote for a Jewish candidate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Sure, I could vote for a Jewish candidate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "What do you make of what's going on with the Palestinians and the Israelis right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "Well, it's a -- it's a difficult situation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "You've both been out there recently I think, to Israel, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "We did.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "How did you find it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "We found it very peaceful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Does it worry you that so many areas of conflict of the world are religion prompted?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "NN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Well, I don't...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Do you like being interviewed or do you find it a bit of a minefield?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "You know what, I enjoy it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Would you be happy with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "Oh, I'd be thrilled, you know, nothing greater than for your children to follow in your legacy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "I mean, are you going to have to keep an extra close eye because you're the Olsteens, everyone be looking to trip them up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "NN", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "Oh, you know what, I never feel like it like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "What's he talking about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "Oh, well, we -- we have good conversations.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "CC", "VBP", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "What's your perfect Friday?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "Well, we like to have a good dinner and we like to either ride our bikes or we like to just hang out and talk or, you know, we may have a few friends over.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "What's the secret?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "And I respect him even more.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "Yes, what's the secret of the Joel Olsteen magic, you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "Well, I think he's a man of what he -- of his word, I think he's a man of what his word, he's -- he's always looking for the best in any situation.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joel Olsteen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "CC", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "Do you agree with all that Joel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "Oh, that and more.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joel?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "NNS", ",", "CC", "NNS", "WDT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", ":", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 596, "question": "You -- you can't ignore it, I mean, you must get some groupies, any?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Oh, I have some kind people, I don't call them groupies, but people that, you know, they feel like you've helped them and you know what, I -- listen...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 599, "question": "Do you get all that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "I don't -- I don't...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "Are you like popular like Tom Jones, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "I don't -- no, not in the work we do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tom Jones"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Victoria"]}, "docId": "111004pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "Ever do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "Well, I -- you know, it's funny because when I -- when I'm out, even by myself, this is what women say to me, oh, Victoria, I love your husband.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]